You're the best sharer of a new stuff, I know.
你最爱分享新玩意儿   我知道
I'm the worst.
我最不好
What do you mean?
你说什么
I mean,
我是说
I didn't wanna share this with you.
我之前不想和你们分享这个
Uh, so that's why you didn't wanna play with us.
呃   这就是你不想跟我们玩的原因
Yeah.
嗯
It's hard to share!
分享太难了
But you know what,
但你知道吗
it's no fun playing with a new toy all alone.
一个人玩新玩具   没意思
Well, it is a pretty cool toy.
呃   它是个很酷的玩具
I don't blame you for not wanting to share it.
我不怪你不想分享它
Well, I want to share it now.
呃   现在我想要分享
So let's play!
那我们玩儿吧
T-bone, catch!
小骨   接着
Got it!
接到了
Throw it to Clifford, T-bone!
扔给克里弗   T骨
Here it comes!
来了哦
This toy is a great toy, Cleo!
这是个很棒的玩具   克里奥
It's even more great when you share with your friends!
当你和朋友分享时   就更棒啦